<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/my_blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:29:03 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/my_blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/my_blog/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:29:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/my_blog/contact/</guid>
      
        <description></description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/my_blog/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:26:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/my_blog/post/first/</guid>
      
        <description></description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/my_blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:01:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/my_blog/about/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As an architectural intern at Michele Tonci Ottieri &amp;amp; Associati (MTOA), I contributed to the design and development of various projects, ranging from residential to commercial buildings, applying my knowledge and skills in landscape architecture, renewable energy, and green building. I graduated with a Master of Architecture degree from Sapienza Università di Roma, where I focused on the integration of natural and artificial elements in urban and rural contexts. I also hold two certifications in renewable energy and green building entrepreneurship and construction project management from Duke University and Columbia University, respectively. Before joining MTOA, I worked as an interior designer at Acado Design, where l designed and implemented innovative and functional solutions for various clients, and as an AutoCAD operator at Zhiyar Beton Company, where I prepared and revised architectural drawings and documents. With more than three years of work experience in the architecture and design industry, I have developed strong competencies in project management, projectt, construction management, AutoCAD, SketchUp, and Revit. I am passionate about creating sustainable and resilient environments that enhance the quality of life and well-being of people and communities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>